Good work on your
competition entries, everyone!
Good work!
Who's up for round two?!
Me!
Senpai, do you want to
walk to the station toge—
Shinozaki-san...
Once we're done...
would you like to come do
something naughty with your senpai?
Something naughty?!
There's a senpai where I work...
who's tiny and sexy—I mean... cute.
Here you go!
Time to eat!
After having some drinks... late at night...
I know it's bad for you,
but I can't resist the sweet siren call...
of ramen!
That's what she meant?!
What's wrong? Aren't you going to eat?
It's just... I didn't expect ramen.
What did you expect, then?
Is she doing this on purpose,
or accidentally?!
Stray Ramen
Thanks for coming!
Thank you for treating me.
You worked really hard on your contest entry.
It's not much, but I wanted to
reward you, as your senpai.
Senpai...
She's nice and always looking out for me.
And that makes me so happy, but...
Are we always just going to be
senpai and kohai?
Man, I am starving!
Y'know what they say about ramen?
Um...
If someone craves ramen late at night,
they've got a strong libido.
What the heck? Like they're not satisfied?
Yep, exactly.
I was really just looking
for some refreshing tea!
R-Right! Tea! I get it!
Anyway! You were about to say something?!
I-It can wait until some other time!
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
My Tiny Senpai
We've got an emergency here
Are you paying attention, me?
There's someone other than me
dancing around inside of my heart
I want to talk to her
I want to touch her
Look, I get it, but for now try to pipe down
What in the world am I doing?
You're right next to me
And this is the perfect chance...
HONEY
I'm trapped by that sweet rich taste
And I don't think I can ever escape
I may as well just sink into it
HONEY
It's another day in your dazzling presence
We may never be
on the same page with this love but
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
#12 A Story About the Tiny Senpai Where I Work
Hayakawa-san, you headed for lunch?
Mind if I join you?
My boss at my job... is pleasant
and friendly to everyone.
Okay... sure.
What's this?
Going to lunch together...
Is this a lunch date?
N-No!
Yep, yep! Let's call it a date!
Don't say something like that at the office!
What if people start spreading weird rumors?!
Considering it's you, Hayakawa-san,
I wouldn't mind.
Wh-Wh-Wh-What's that mean?!
Considering who said it,
it's probably nothing significant, but...
Ugh! You just had to
say something, Katase-san!
Senpai!
I found my wallet, so let's go.
It's a date!
It's not!
Zakishino!
Rainbow Sweet Potato Tarts
Mensore! Here's some Okinawa stuff.
Thanks.
Did you enjoy the resort?
Are you hitting on me?
Aw, but I've got a girlfriend!
Ugh...
I was transferred,
but I used my paid time off, Yuri-tan!
I'm so glad, Masa-tan!
Who even does that?
It was... a real blast...
Console me, Zakishino!
Shinozaki-san!
Could I bug you for a bit after work?
40th Anniversary
A Meowtaro game?
Yep! My anthropomorphized
hottie Meowtaro game is finished!
Doki Doki
Meowtaro
~Our Academy of Romance~
Start
It's finally done!
And so...
I was hoping to have Shinozaki
the gamer play it for a bit!
Well, let's get to it, then.
Yeah.
Out Front of School
Meowtaro:
Hey there. I'm Meowtaro. Nice to meet you.
So you try to romance Meowtaro
from the perspective of a girl?
Looks like it.
I hear you're quite the cook.
I'd love to try something you've made.
Restaurant
Meat
Fish
Vegetables
Fruit
Affection
Meowtaro:
You've gotta pick the menu...?
Even if he's anthropomorphized,
Meowtaro's a cat.
He probably likes fish, right?
Probably!
Fish it is, then.
Fish
Affection
Fish, huh? That's not bad, but...
Meowtaro:
Restaurant
Huh?
That wasn't the reaction
I was expecting.
Meowtaro is the heir to a major corporation.
He eats fish every day, so he's tired of it!
I don't think that's part of the backstory...
The best choice is fruit!
Restaurant
Fruit
Affection
Meowtaro:
I've never had anything like it...
You must know about a world
I'm unfamiliar with.
What does that even mean?
What are you all doing?
Kurusu-san.
Office hours are over.
Why are you all here?
I was having them try out
the Meowtaro game I made.
Want to try it, Kurusu-san?
A Meowtaro game?!
I do! I want to play! Please let me play it!
Meowtaro:
I could steal these lips
in a heartbeat.
This is it...
Who?
This is anthropomorphic hottie Meowtaro!
It'll let us develop
the latent otome game market!
Meowtaro...? Hot...? Anthropomorphic...?
My Meowtaro... what in the world...?
This isn't development. It's pandering.
It doesn't convey a fraction of
Meowtaro's actual appeal.
It's more likely to chase off
existing fans than develop new ones.
It's idiocy.
Do you really think we can
open up new opportunities
by being so beholden to old fans
that we never try anything new?
It's a question of methodology.
This would honestly be better off
as a completely distinct project...
Let's keep on playing, Zakishino!
Roof
Affection
Meowtaro:
The culture festival is ending...
There's something I need to tell to you.
Are we gonna get a confession
after the festival?!
I'm not sure. It feels a little too soon
for things to be ending...
But it's a private meeting on the rooftop!
On the rooftop...
Meeting in private...
That sounds familiar.
Roof
Affection
Meowtaro:
Let's always be good senpai and kohai, okay?
This line...
That line...
Let's always be good coworkers, okay?
It's kinda similar!
Aw, man, we got rejected before the confession.
Rejected...
Before confessing...
Rejected?
Before confessing...?
I rejected him?!
That's not what I was trying to do...!
Is that what Shinozaki-san felt at the time?!
I really was rejected?!
That's what really happened?!
And after I had tried to forget all about it!
What's with you two?
Hold it right there. It's too soon to give up.
I know you two must have realized it.
There's still a while before the ending,
and you haven't confessed yet...
So you can still seal the deal yet!
Your chance is still out there...
Or do you mean to tell me...
that you two don't love Meowtaro that much?!
I mean, we don't.
Hadn't confessed yet...
There's still a chance...
I hadn't confessed yet!
There's still a chance!
That's right! We haven't been rejected yet!
I agree!
Is there a reason you guys are so into this?
It's not even the real Meowtaro.
That video game was fun.
It sure was.
I liked how they ended up
together in the end.
Yeah.
Shinozaki-san.
What was it that you wanted to tell me before?
I was wondering if we'd always
just be a senpai and a kohai.
I remember saying that we should always
just be good coworkers before.
But now...
Maybe now, it'd be okay if things changed.
Like, for instance...
We... We...
We could be... friends.
I mean, we already get along well, but—
Does that mean...
Does that mean you wouldn't mind if we spent
more time together in our personal lives?
Yes.
I can invite you out shopping?
Sure!
And for lunch on days off?
If anything, I'd think that's
a natural thing for friends to do!
A-And if I send you a text asking
"Are you busy?" for no reason...
We're friends, so it's not a problem!
We could send pictures of us wearing
new clothes we've bought!
That sounds like the kind of thing
friends should do together!
Because we're friends!
We're friends!
Yes, we are!
And so they've obtained the new
rationalization... of friendship.
H-Hang on, Manager! Don't turn into
sugar and blow away again!
Sugar!
My Tiny Senpai.
Sunpick 40th Anniversary
My Tiny Senpai!
Yeah!
Senpai!
Good morning.
Senpai and I...
Shinozaki-san and I...
are friends now.
Product Development
Group 2
Not just coworkers...
But a personal relationship, too.
I've uploaded the data.
Okay. Let me just confirm it.
Senpai and I are friends now.
Shinozaki-san and I are friends now.
And yet...
Nothing's changed!
I want to take her out for dinner or something
outside work, but don't know when to ask!
I bought new clothes
and even took selfies in them!
But I don't know when
I should send them!
I mean, I've never had a female friend before!
I mean, I've never had a male friend before!
How exactly do I do anything?!
I don't know how to do anything!
If only we had...
even the slightest new development...
Sounds like Okinawa was pretty rough.
Tell me about it. Everywhere
I turned, people were in heat...
Is it all right that I'm joining for lunch?
Sure. We should get together
for lunch every now and then.
Th-Thank you.
I want to make something happen,
but I'm not sure how to approach it...
The timing...
Still, I'm sure getting
to go to Okinawa was nice.
Are you feeling a bit more refreshed?
I guess a little...
Golden Week is coming up soon,
so I'd like to go somewhere.
Hey, do any of you have plans?
This timing!
I'm not really doing anything.
But it'd be nice to go out with some friends.
Obvious Bait
Nothing on my end.
But I'd really like to have fun with friends.
Obvious Bait
Now I know they don't have any plans...
I'm not doing jack, either.
I've got some. Every year, I go to
an amusement park with a friend from high school.
An amusement park?!
We wear matching outfits...
Matching outfits...
Nice!
And then buy merchandise to
commemorate the occasion...
Commemorative merch...
Nice!
Going to an amusement park sounds fantastic.
It's like friendship utopia.
You think? There are a lot of people
with their kids, too.
But we're doing something extra this time.
Check this out...
We've reserved a room at the park's hotel!
H-Hotel?!
There's a private lounge with a bar where
you can look at the park while drinking.
A private lounge with a bar...
Shinozaki-san.
Here's to looking at you, Senpai.
We sit on the bed and talk about the day...
On the bed...
Senpai...
This was a lot of fun, huh?
And then we wrap it up by enjoying
the room's open air bath!
T-Together...
in a bath?!
And then in the morning...
Yamagishi-san!
Tthat seems a little unsavory,
even for friends!
That's right! I-I mean, bathing together...
Seems pretty normal to me.
I just think it's a little too soon for that!
Maybe after the relationship's matured some!
You think?
We do!
Oh, wait, are you two...
embarrassed about bathing around others?
I wouldn't say that...
I'd be kind of glad to, actually...
These two are actually lewd
I mean, I've known her since high school, so...
A friend from your school days, huh?
That sounds like a lot of fun.
The hotel took me by surprise, but...
an amusement park... That really sounds nice.
It might be too soon for a hotel, but...
an amusement park? Nice idea.
Talking about it has made me want to go.
Me, too!
In that case...
No.
Theme parks are the domain
of other characters...
Money earned from Meowtaro...
can't be spent on others... ever.
Do you not like amusement parks, Kurusu-san?
It's not that.
Meowtaro Land Project Outline
I wanna make Meowtaro Land.
So if anything, you love them.
In that case, shouldn't you
check other places out
as a way of gathering intel?
Instead of trying to make
something from scratch,
it'd be a good idea to use
a successful model as reference.
It'll help you come up
with unique ideas, too.
That's a fair point.
In that case, since it's come up,
why don't we all go during Golden Week?
All of us...
That sounds good.
Let's all go together!
Okay, then! If we're all going, I wanna go, too!
So, when should we do it?
Let's see...
May
Sunday         Monday        Tuesday      Wednesday     Thursday         Friday           Saturday
Hayakawa X
Katase X
Shinozaki X
Yamagishi ♀ X
Hayakawa X
Yamagishi ♂ X
Kurusu X
I guess our schedules don't match up...
Guess we won't be able
to all go during Golden Week.
Well, what about during summer vacation, then?
Since there's more time until then,
it should be easier
to make our schedules match.
It's on hold, then.
I wanted to go to that amusement park...
Senpai!
Shinozaki-san...
U-Um, I know the scheduling
didn't work out for everyone, but...
Would you... well...
as friends... we could...
What Yamagishi-san was talking about
sounded nice! So... maybe...
The amusement park.
Let's go to the amusement park together.
Yeah!
You said you were always free.
But then you had a day
where you couldn't... Why?
Well, let's just chalk it up
to doing the bro thing.
The cute shoes I bought
or the sneakers I've broken in...
Picking the right look for visiting an amusement park with that special someone
Share    Tweet    Like
Okay!
The fashionable look...
Or the casual one...
Which should I go with?
You got a date?
Don't just show up like that!
You  always spend Golden Week every year
back at home, but this year you didn't.
So I came to check on you.
I see... a date with Shiorin, then.
It's not a date! We're just going to
the amusement park together!
Sounds like... a date.
Well, it's not!
I haven't confessed to her
or started going out!
We're really just going as friends!
Then, you think...
going to an amusement park
is something that friends do?
Y-Yeah.
Amusement Park Gate
Amusement Park Gate, Amusement Park Gate.
I got here faster than I expected.
Maybe I should find a café...
I guess we were on the same train.
Cute!
I woke up a bit early.
M-Me, too.
You seem different from usual.
Your hair's up, and you're wearing pants.
Well, it's an amusement park...
I figured we'd be walking a lot...
I've got sneakers on, too.
So do I.
We'll probably be walking more than
some hiking trips, honestly.
Yeah!
We're a little early, but let's get in line.
Let's!
There's a senpai where I work...
who is tiny and cute.
I guess we should head home.
I guess so.
But first...
How about it?
Something to remember the occasion.
I-It's been a while since I've been
to an amusement park with a friend!
Do you not want to?
I didn't say that!
Want me to take it for you?
Thank you so—
Manager?!
Along with my sister and Hayakawa?!
Why are you here?!
Li'l bro, you said as much yourself.
Amusement parks are for visiting with your friends.
And thus...
Chihiro, let's go to the amusement park!
Let's invite Hayakawa-san, too, then.
Huh? The amusement park?
And so, the three of us had a great time.
Why am I here...?
I... see.
Okay, now get closer together!
Shiorin! Shiorin!
Hayakawa-san, did you enjoy yourself?
Well... I guess I did.
Things got kind of busy
at the end there, but...
Thinking of coming again?
I guess I am.